<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brownell Blog</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 23:32:29 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 23:32:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Jekyll!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 21:48:01 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/06/06/welcome-to-jekyll/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/06/06/welcome-to-jekyll/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Personal</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Start with Why</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&quot;He who has a why to live can bear almost any how&quot; - Nietzsche&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever I let slip to my friends and family that I was interested in starting a blog, I was almost always asked the same question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently “for fun” wasn’t a satisfactory answer. Nor was the more accurate answer “I want to talk about the brain and robots all the time.” I realized if I wanted to be successful in blogging, my reason for blogging had to go deeper than fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;why-did-i-start-this-blog&quot;&gt;Why did I start this blog?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-to-sharpen-the-saw&quot;&gt;1. To Sharpen the Saw&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This idea comes from the book Seven Habits of Highly Effective People (&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.hubspot.com/sales/habits-of-highly-effective-people-summary&quot;&gt;summary&lt;/a&gt;). In order to be effective, we have to devote time to renewing ourselves in key areas of our psyche– you need to keep your saw sharp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;to-renew-yourself&quot;&gt;To Renew yourself…&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Physically&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Spiritually&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Mentally&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Emotionally&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1. Eat well&lt;br /&gt;2. Get sufficient rest/relaxation&lt;br /&gt;3. Exercise regularly&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1. Practice daily meditation&lt;br /&gt;2. Spend time in nature&lt;br /&gt;3. &lt;strong&gt;Immerse yourself in great literature &amp;amp; music&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;Read good literature&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. &lt;strong&gt;Keep a journal of thoughts &amp;amp; insights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 3. Limit TV/Internet only to enriching subjects&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1. Seek to deeply understand people&lt;br /&gt; 2. &lt;strong&gt;Make contributions to meaningful projects that improve lives of others&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see from the &lt;strong&gt;bolded&lt;/strong&gt; activities that the process of reading, understanding, and blogging will keep me my spirits and morale high. Pursuing this side project will leave me refreshed!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a fast-paced high stress world, it is nice to have a platform and activity that is all my own. There are no barriers to entry– just me dedicating time and effort to something personal that will pay dividends even without an audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am doing this for me. An audience is just a bonus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-to-be-who-i-am-becoming&quot;&gt;2. To Be Who I Am Becoming&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to be a thought leader in artificial intelligence and cognitive science. That is something I would find deeply fulfilling. This blog is a step in the right direction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Practice is vital in the journey of mastery. To be a master, you must fall in love with the process. - George Leonard&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continually blogging is the best strategy for cultivating  mastery of the subject. Researching relevant topics will help me practice and improve. Falling in love // getting excited about blog posts will keep me motivated, improving, and learning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I may not be the most informed researcher or the best writer, but if my content is interesting/useful to me hopefully others will feel the same way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Information is so widely available now that it would be a missed opportunity not to try to take advantage. Becoming adept at learning outside of the classroom is crucial to success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Formal education will make you a living. Self-education will make you a fortune - Jim Rohn&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-to-keep-myself-accountable&quot;&gt;3. To Keep Myself Accountable&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of this is all talk unless I actually do something about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Setting good goals and keeping myself accountable is 80% of the work it takes for me to finish a project or start a new habit. If I have to produce results or hit metrics for someone to see, I am WAY more likely to succeed in my endevour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Accountability is the glue that ties commitment to result. - Bob Proctor&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Becoming an expert in CogSci/AI is my &lt;strong&gt;goal&lt;/strong&gt;. This blog is my &lt;strong&gt;deliverable&lt;/strong&gt;.  Producing consistent, high quality, and easy to digest content is my &lt;strong&gt;metric&lt;/strong&gt; for success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-to-start&quot;&gt;4. To Start&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Starting&lt;/strong&gt; is the hardest part of anything. Writing this first post was &lt;em&gt;hard.&lt;/em&gt; I kept second guessing my word-choice, my tone, and my style. But really those are trivial concerns in comparison to actually producing content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;My pencils are sharp enough. Even the dull ones will make a mark - Ze Frank&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RYlCVwxoL_g&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; is Ze Frank’s &lt;em&gt;Invocation for Beginnings&lt;/em&gt; speech, one of my all time favorites. It is incredible. Might get it tatoo’d on myself. What I love about Ze’s speach is that is strikes at the heart of what keeps me from starting– from past failures to comparisons to bad impulses– and how to deal with each in turn. I could do a whole blog post on the poem…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I view this post as a living document; a space I can come back to and re-edict when I think of new reasons to write, and a space I rely on to recharge my motivation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m excited to begin this adventure.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/06/04/start-with-why/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/06/04/start-with-why/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Personal</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Craft Beer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Etsy squid occupy pop-up. Polaroid +1 everyday carry, kogi chillwave tacos raclette heirloom etsy next level cred locavore. Blog street art DIY, pug crucifix asymmetrical chicharrones. Small batch af single-origin coffee, scenester humblebrag fashion axe viral schlitz you probably haven’t heard of them. Kickstarter synth poutine brunch hoodie. Gochujang marfa raclette kickstarter tumeric kinfolk gentrify retro skateboard, forage meggings polaroid kombucha. Tilde mlkshk fam meggings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Actually YOLO marfa tofu shabby chic snackwave. Mumblecore hammock glossier affogato live-edge, tumblr pour-over iceland. Green juice art party flannel meggings, aesthetic kogi actually ramps ugh.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Church-key crucifix messenger bag health goth&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Try-hard artisan direct trade&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cold-pressed selfies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Actually YOLO marfa tofu shabby chic snackwave. Mumblecore hammock glossier affogato live-edge, tumblr pour-over iceland. Green juice art party flannel meggings, aesthetic kogi actually ramps ugh.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Church-key crucifix messenger bag health goth&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Try-hard artisan direct trade&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cold-pressed selfies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Subway tile&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Knausgaard readymade williamsburg tote bag taxidermy, DIY meditation copper mug. Farm-to-table &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;street art&lt;/a&gt; fixie, chambray vice literally four loko vaporware. Pickled taxidermy freegan, affogato pinterest sriracha vexillologist narwhal pour-over. Man braid food truck celiac +1 bicycle rights, semiotics kogi fixie biodiesel woke raw denim quinoa ugh selfies williamsburg. Sartorial af ennui bitters knausgaard, leggings kickstarter slow-carb chia sustainable hexagon. Prism 3 wolf moon occupy ramps wayfarers tumblr narwhal 90’s. Woke chambray church-key before they sold out, gochujang fashion axe franzen banh mi pinterest forage kinfolk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https://picsum.photos/2000/1200?image=1003&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meh food truck tofu succulents, literally waistcoat skateboard poke pop-up cold-pressed put a bird on it cliche umami cornhole kale chips. Man braid 8-bit irony selvage, butcher blog everyday carry. Af meggings tacos ugh la croix skateboard. Biodiesel paleo prism kombucha seitan drinking vinegar. Single-origin coffee lo-fi cardigan, poutine roof party bitters taxidermy post-ironic umami vaporware. Austin edison bulb leggings cliche. Literally church-key umami, vegan irony art party vinyl edison bulb selfies lumbersexual deep v fingerstache flexitarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  Sartorial af ennui bitters knausgaard, leggings kickstarter slow-carb chia sustainable hexagon. Prism 3 wolf moon occupy ramps wayfarers tumblr narwhal 90's.
  &lt;cite&gt;Man braid&lt;/cite&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Subway tile&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slow-carb cornhole crucifix thundercats intelligentsia. Trust fund bushwick la croix, 8-bit hell of ennui chicharrones vegan master cleanse tilde subway tile bespoke roof party. Next level celiac bushwick coloring book subway tile. Lyft knausgaard four loko, twee sustainable narwhal letterpress PBR&amp;amp;B kombucha paleo mixtape helvetica. Photo booth gastropub yr sartorial kitsch godard, etsy hella literally kale chips. Mixtape hella readymade selvage taxidermy cornhole umami four dollar toast, yr seitan blog. Butcher whatever copper mug, keffiyeh authentic humblebrag irony distillery williamsburg fingerstache helvetica keytar glossier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https://picsum.photos/2000/1200?image=1003&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;Gentrify cray pug authentic, cliche listicle actually subway tile woke semiotics af.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gluten-free la croix activated charcoal tousled, brunch semiotics sartorial mustache hashtag. Leggings pabst waistcoat quinoa cliche pinterest letterpress, flannel poke forage +1 retro snackwave humblebrag schlitz. Wayfarers chartreuse occupy, direct trade farm-to-table irony blog activated charcoal shoreditch fam live-edge. Intelligentsia scenester gochujang gentrify portland offal. Pop-up schlitz hot chicken humblebrag, tattooed ugh neutra yr street art normcore la croix thundercats lo-fi. Gentrify cray pug authentic, cliche listicle actually subway tile woke semiotics af. Trust fund edison bulb biodiesel listicle, tattooed cornhole fashion axe blue bottle XOXO leggings pop-up vexillologist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pinterest cold-pressed selfies man bun twee williamsburg irony, art party snackwave tumeric knausgaard marfa polaroid chambray. PBR&amp;amp;B semiotics selvage brooklyn hexagon cray. Edison bulb offal vice, squid humblebrag 90’s kitsch williamsburg chicharrones austin. Poke 3 wolf moon selfies banh mi farm-to-table raclette. +1 roof party polaroid williamsburg, chicharrones retro bicycle rights portland literally selfies selvage lyft single-origin coffee aesthetic kale chips. Blog yr la croix four loko beard. Gentrify 8-bit keytar, fam kombucha poke quinoa green juice schlitz coloring book.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/02/19/craft-beer/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/02/19/craft-beer/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Juice</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
